[
    {"question": "ğŸ‡§ğŸ‡·", "response": "Brasil" },
    {"question": "ğŸ‡ºğŸ‡¸", "response": "Estados Unidos" },
    {"question": "ğŸ‡¨ğŸ‡¦", "response": "CanadÃ¡" },
    {"question": "ğŸ‡¬ğŸ‡§", "response": "Reino Unido" },
    {"question": "ğŸ‡¯ğŸ‡µ", "response": "JapÃ£o" },
    {"question": "ğŸ‡¨ğŸ‡³", "response": "China" },
    {"question": "ğŸ‡©ğŸ‡ª", "response": "Alemanha" },
    {"question": "ğŸ‡«ğŸ‡·", "response": "FranÃ§a" },
    {"question": "ğŸ‡®ğŸ‡¹", "response": "ItÃ¡lia" },
    {"question": "ğŸ‡ªğŸ‡¸", "response": "Espanha" },
    {"question": "ğŸ‡¦ğŸ‡º", "response": "AustrÃ¡lia" },
    {"question": "ğŸ‡§ğŸ‡ª", "response": "BÃ©lgica" },
    {"question": "ğŸ‡·ğŸ‡º", "response": "RÃºssia" },
    {"question": "ğŸ‡¿ğŸ‡¦", "response": "Ãfrica do Sul" },
    {"question": "ğŸ‡²ğŸ‡½", "response": "MÃ©xico" },
    {"question": "ğŸ‡¦ğŸ‡·", "response": "Argentina" },
    {"question": "ğŸ‡¨ğŸ‡´", "response": "ColÃ´mbia" },
    {"question": "ğŸ‡¸ğŸ‡¦", "response": "ArÃ¡bia Saudita" },
    {"question": "ğŸ‡®ğŸ‡³", "response": "Ãndia" },
    {"question": "ğŸ‡®ğŸ‡©", "response": "IndonÃ©sia" }
]
